Art Buchwald Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Writings, 1948-2006 (Box 49-132)
  Material types include articles, book manuscripts, book reviews, columns, correspondence, digital files, lists, newspaper clippings, photographs, and printed matter.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of publication and alphabetically by title or topic or chronologically therein. File structure of the digital content included in this series was maintained as received.
  - Articles (Box 49)
    - 1950-1969, (11 folders) (Box 49)
    - 1970-1999, (11 folders) (Box 50)
    - 2001-2006, undated, (2 folders) (Box 51)
  - Books (Box 51)
    - ... And Then I Told the President: The Secret Papers of Art Buchwald, 1965 (Box 51)
    - Art Buchwald's Paris, 1954-1955 (Box 51)
    - Beating Around the Bush (Box 51)
      - Book talk, Martha's Vineyard, Mass., video files, 2005, mss86197_178_018
      - Correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 51)
      - Draft, circa 2004, (2 folders) (Box 51)
    - The Bollo Caper: A Fable for Children of All Ages (Box 51)
      - Correspondence (Box 51)
        - 1973-1974, (1 folder) (Box 51)
        - 1982-1985, (1 folder) (Box 52)
      - Galley proofs, 1974 (Box 52)
      - Illustrations, 1983 (Box 52)
      - Letters and drawings from children, 1973-1978 See also Container OV 7, Drawings (Box 52)
      - Reinert, Rick, special television production for American Broadcasting Company's "Kid Time," 1985, mss86197_178_207
      - Reviews, 1974-1983 (Box 52)
    - The Brave Coward, reviews, 1956-1957 (Box 52)
    - The Buchwald Stops Here (Box 52)
      - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 52)
      - Rejected columns, 1976-1977 (Box 52)
      - Reviews, 1978-1979, (2 folders) (Box 52)
    - Counting Sheep: The Log and the Complete Play: Sheep on the Runway (Box 52)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1971, 1982 (Box 52)
      - Draft, circa 1970 (Box 52)
      - Reviews, 1970-1971 (Box 53)
    - "The Diary of a Continental," 1955 (Box 53)
    - Don't Forget to Write, 1960-1963, (2 folders) (Box 53)
    - Down the Seine and Up the Potomac with Art Buchwald (Box 53)
      - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 53)
      - Drafts of introduction and dedications, 1977 (Box 53)
      - Lists of columns and articles for possible inclusion, circa 1977 (Box 53)
      - Reviews, 1977-1978, (2 folders) (Box 53)
    - The Establishment Is Alive and Well in Washington, 1970 (Box 54)
    - Getting High in Government Circles, 1970-1971, (2 folders) (Box 54)
    - A Gift from the Boys (novel) (Box 54)
      - Correspondence (Box 54)
        - General, 1958-1962, (2 folders) (Box 54)
        - Lalonde, Gaby, 1957, undated (Box 54)
      - Drafts (Box 54)
        - Final draft of novel, 1957, (4 folders) (Box 54)
        - Screenplay, undated, (1 folder) (Box 54)
        - Screenplay, undated, (2 folders) (Box 55)
      - Miscellany, circa 1958 (Box 55)
      - Reviews of novel and movie Surprise Package, 1958-1960 (Box 55)
      - Surprise Package film, 1960, mss86197_178_218
    - "Gogol Eats," 1992, 2002 (Box 55)
    - Have I Ever Lied to You?, 1968-1969 (Box 55)
    - How Much Is That in Dollars?, circa 1960-1962, (5 folders) (Box 55)
    - "I Am Not a Crook," 1973-1976, (2 folders) (Box 55)
    - I Chose Capitol Punishment, 1962-1964 (Box 56)
    - I Chose Caviar, 1957-1962 (Box 56)
    - I Never Danced at the White House, 1973-1975, (2 folders) (Box 56)
    - I Think I Don't Remember (Box 56)
      - Complimentary book list, 1987 (Box 56)
      - Correspondence, 1986-1988, (2 folders) (Box 56)
      - Publicity packet, 1987 See also Container OV 17, Photograph collage (Box 56)
      - Reviews, 1988-1989 (Box 56)
    - Irving's Delight: At Last! A Cat Story for the Whole Family! (Box 56)
      - Correspondence, 1975-1984, (2 folders) (Box 56)
      - Illustrations, 1975 (Box 56)
      - Reviews, 1975-1976 (Box 56)
    - Is It Safe to Drink the Water?, 1962-1963 (Box 56)
    - Laid Back in Washington (Box 57)
      - Complimentary book lists, 1981 (Box 57)
      - Correspondence, 1980-1983, (2 folders) (Box 57)
      - Photographs for book jacket, 1981 (Box 57)
      - Reviews, 1981-1983 (Box 57)
    - Lighten Up, George (Box 57)
      - Complimentary book lists, 1991 (Box 57)
      - Correspondence, 1991-1993, (2 folders) (Box 57)
      - Draft, edited, 1991-1994, (2 folders) (Box 57)
      - Lists and edited copies of columns, 1989-1991, (2 folders) (Box 58)
      - Reviews and book jacket, 1991 (Box 58)
    - More Caviar, 1958-1959, (2 folders) (Box 58)
    - Oh, To Be a Swinger, 1969-1972, (2 folders) (Box 58)
    - Paris After Dark, 1950-1958, (2 folders) (Box 58)
    - "Read Between the Lines," unpublished collection of letters, 2002, (2 folders) (Box 58)
    - "Read Between the Lines," unpublished collection of letters, 2002, (5 folders) (Box 59)
    - Son of the Great Society, 1965-1967 (Box 59)
    - Stella in Heaven: Almost a Novel (Box 59)
      - Complimentary book and invitation lists, 2000 (Box 59)
      - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 59)
      - Drafts, digital files
        - 1996, mss86197_178_039
        - 1998, mss86197_178_094; mss86197_178_102; mss86197_178_230
      - Drafts, paper copies, the drafting sequence of which is uncertain, 1998-1999, (6 folders) (Box 60)
      - Drafts, paper copies, the drafting sequence of which is uncertain, 1998-1999, (3 folders) (Box 61)
      - Reviews, 2000 (Box 61)
    - Washington Is Leaking, 1976-1977, (2 folders) (Box 61)
    - We'll Laugh Again (Box 61)
      - Correspondence, 2001-2002, (2 folders) (Box 61)
      - Draft, digital file, 2001, mss86197_178_221
      - Drafts, paper copies, 2001, (3 folders) (Box 62)
      - Eliminated columns, 1991-2001 (Box 62)
      - Reviews, publicity, and complimentary book lists, 2002 (Box 63)
    - While Reagan Slept (Box 63)
      - Complimentary book lists, 1983 (Box 63)
      - Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 63)
      - Illustrations by Steve Mendelson, circa 1983 (Box 63)
      - Reviews, 1983 (Box 63)
    - Whose Rose Garden Is It Anyway? (Box 63)
      - Complimentary book lists, 1989 (Box 63)
      - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 63)
      - Illustrations by Steve Mendelson, 1989 (Box 63)
      - Lists and copies of columns, 1987-1989 (Box 63)
      - Possible book titles, 1989 (Box 63)
      - Reviews and publicity, 1989 (Box 64)
    - You Can Fool All of the People All of the Time (Box 64)
      - Complimentary book lists, 1987 (Box 64)
      - Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 64)
      - Humor on Wry, audiobook, selected readings, 1993, mss86197_178_213
      - Lists and copies of columns, 1983-1985 (Box 64)
      - Photographs for book jacket, 1985 (Box 64)
      - Reviews, 1985-1986 (Box 64)
  - Columns (Box 64)
    - Alphabetical (Box 64)
      - Airlines and flying, 1975-1982 (Box 64)
      - Banking and finance, 1979-1983 (Box 64)
      - "Bonnie and Clyde," 1968 (Box 64)
      - Business, 1990-1991 (Box 64)
      - Cannes Film Festival, 1961 (Box 64)
      - Cars, 1974-1985 (Box 64)
      - Central Intelligence Agency, circa 1966-1968, 1983 (Box 64)
      - Computers, 1975-1980 (Box 64)
      - Cronkite, Walter, 1979-1980 (Box 64)
      - Energy, 1977-1978 (Box 64)
      - Environment, 1970, 1981-1991 (Box 64)
      - Fathers, 1970-1980 (Box 64)
      - Food and drink, circa 1981 (Box 64)
      - Football, 1975-1980 (Box 64)
      - Frequently requested columns, 1962-1997 (Box 64)
      - Gasoline prices, 1979 (Box 64)
      - Health, medicine, doctors, 1968-1993 (Box 64)
      - Kissinger, Henry, 1975-1976 (Box 64)
      - Lawyers, 1977-1981 (Box 64)
      - Never used columns, circa 1980-2002, undated, (4 folders) (Box 65)
      - Oil, 1974-1980 (Box 65)
      - "Prayer for Tourists," undated See Container OV 7, Linen print (Box 65)
      - Presidential elections, 1980 (Box 65)
      - Real estate, 1980 (Box 65)
      - Silver and gold, 1974-1980 (Box 65)
      - Sports, 1982-1993 (Box 65)
      - Story ideas, undated (Box 65)
      - Students, 1963-1968 (Box 65)
      - Television, 1974-1979 (Box 65)
      - Thanksgiving Day (Box 65)
        - Paper file, 1959-2001, (2 folders) (Box 65)
        - "Merci Donnant Musical" audio files, undated, mss86197_178_199
      - Vietnam War, 1963-1968 (Box 65)
      - Visiting Americans, tourism, 1951-1959 (Box 65)
      - Women and surnames, 1982 (Box 65)
    - Chronological (Box 65)
      - 1949, (2 folders) (Box 65)
      - 1950-1951, (10 folders) (Box 66)
      - 1952-1953, (12 folders) (Box 67)
      - 1953-1954, (12 folders) (Box 68)
      - 1954-1955, (13 folders) (Box 69)
      - 1955-1957, (14 folders) (Box 70)
      - 1957-1959, (17 folders) (Box 71)
      - 1959-1961, (16 folders) (Box 72)
      - 1961-1963, (14 folders) (Box 73)
      - 1963-1964, (16 folders) (Box 74)
      - 1965-1966, (15 folders) (Box 75)
      - 1966-1967, (13 folders) (Box 76)
      - 1967-1969, (13 folders) (Box 77)
      - 1969-1970, (14 folders) (Box 78)
      - 1970-1972, (13 folders) (Box 79)
      - 1972-1973, (14 folders) (Box 80)
      - 1973-1974, (13 folders) (Box 81)
      - 1974-1975, (11 folders) (Box 82)
      - 1975-1976, (12 folders) (Box 83)
      - 1976-1977, (14 folders) (Box 84)
      - 1977-1978, (15 folders) (Box 85)
      - 1978-1979, (15 folders) (Box 86)
      - 1980-1981, (14 folders) (Box 87)
      - 1981-1982, (11 folders) (Box 88)
      - 1982-1984, (10 folders) (Box 89)
      - 1984-1985, (11 folders) (Box 90)
      - 1985-1987, (15 folders) (Box 91)
      - 1987-1989, (17 folders) (Box 92)
      - 1990-1992, (20 folders) (Box 93)
      - 1992-1997, (17 folders) (Box 94)
      - 1997-1998, undated, (7 folders) (Box 95)
    - Drafts (Box 95)
      - circa 1950-1976, (9 folders) (Box 95)
      - 1979-1981, (7 folders) (Box 96)
      - 1982-1983, (6 folders) (Box 97)
      - 1983-1985, (6 folders) (Box 98)
      - 1985-1986, (6 folders) (Box 99)
      - 1987-1991, (7 folders) (Box 100)
      - 1991-1992, (6 folders) (Box 101)
      - 1992, (6 folders) (Box 102)
      - 1993, (6 folders) (Box 103)
      - 1994, (7 folders) (Box 104)
      - 1995, (8 folders) (Box 105)
      - 1995-1996, (7 folders) (Box 106)
      - 1996-1997, (7 folders) (Box 107)
      - 1997-1998, (9 folders) (Box 108)
      - 1998-1999, (9 folders) (Box 109)
      - 1999-2000, (11 folders) (Box 110)
      - 2000-2001, (11 folders) (Box 111)
      - 2001-2002, (10 folders) (Box 112)
      - 2002-2003, (11 folders) (Box 113)
      - 2003-2004, (12 folders) (Box 114)
      - 2004-2006, (12 folders) (Box 115)
      - 2006, undated, (5 folders) (Box 116)
    - Translations (Box 116)
      - Chinese, 1975-1979 (Box 116)
      - Czech, 1964 (Box 116)
      - Danish, 1958 (Box 116)
      - Dutch, 1958 (Box 116)
      - Finnish, 1958 (Box 116)
      - German, 1960-1968 (Box 116)
      - Italian, 1958 (Box 116)
      - Portuguese, 1958 (Box 116)
      - Russian ("Iron Curtain") (Box 116)
        - 1958-1964, (3 folders) (Box 116)
        - 1965-1966, (8 folders) (Box 117)
        - 1966-1967, (10 folders) (Box 118)
        - 1967-1979, (11 folders) (Box 119)
        - 1980-1996, undated, (9 folders) (Box 120)
      - Spanish, 1963 (Box 120)
  - Memoirs (Box 120)
    - I'll Always Have Paris (Box 120)
      - Book tour and parties, 1996 (Box 120)
      - Complimentary book lists, 1996 (Box 120)
      - Correspondence (Box 120)
        - 1996, (3 folders) (Box 120)
        - 1996-2002, (3 folders) (Box 121)
      - Drafts, digital files
        - 1994, mss86197_178_047; mss86197_178_048; mss86197_178_067; mss86197_178_112; mss86197_178_113; Digital ID mss86197_178_113 contains a mix of encrypted and unencrypted files. The encrypted files are inaccessible.; mss86197_178_133
        - 1994-1996, mss86197_178_028; mss86197_178_041; mss86197_178_090
        - 1995, mss86197_178_040; mss86197_178_045; mss86197_178_055; mss86197_178_077; mss86197_178_089; mss86197_178_103; mss86197_178_121; mss86197_178_148
      - Drafts, paper copies (Box 121)
        - circa 1993-1994, (5 folders) (Box 121)
        - 1994-1996, (7 folders) (Box 122)
        - 1996-1997, (3 folders) (Box 123)
      - Miscellaneous notes, draft pages, and background material, 1952-1962, 1978-1995 (Box 123)
      - Reviews, 1996-1997, (2 folders) (Box 123)
    - Leaving Home (Box 123)
      - Background correspondence and research, 1962, 1975, 1992-1994 (Box 123)
      - Complimentary book lists, 1993-1994 (Box 123)
      - Correspondence, largely with publisher (Box 123)
        - 1992, (1 folder) (Box 123)
        - 1993-1996, (3 folders) (Box 124)
      - Drafts, digital files
        - 1990-1993, mss86197_178_090
        - 1991-1993, mss86197_178_070; mss86197_178_093; mss86197_178_120
        - 1992, mss86197_178_056; mss86197_178_074; mss86197_178_083; mss86197_178_135; mss86197_178_129; mss86197_178_152; mss86197_178_185; mss86197_178_224
        - 1992-1993, mss86197_178_030; mss86197_178_034
        - 1993, mss86197_178_064; mss86197_178_080; mss86197_178_081; mss86197_178_115; mss86197_178_147; mss86197_178_190
      - Drafts, paper copies (Box 124)
        - 1989-1992, (5 folders) (Box 124)
        - 1993, (2 folders) (Box 125)
      - Galley proofs, 1993, (2 folders) (Box 125)
      - Invitations to speak, 1994 (Box 125)
      - Letter to sister, 1993 (Box 125)
      - Letters from friends, 1993-1994, (3 folders) (Box 125)
      - Letters from readers, 1994-1998, (12 folders) (Box 126)
      - Photographs, 1920s, 1940s, 1993 (Box 127)
      - Publicity and book parties, 1993-1994, 2002 See also Container OV 13, Crank toy, (2 folders) (Box 127)
      - Reviews, 1993-1994, (3 folders) (Box 127)
    - "Revenge Is Sweet," circa 2004, (3 folders) (Box 127)
    - Too Soon to Say Goodbye (Box 127)
      - Galley proofs, 2006, (1 folder) (Box 127)
      - Galley proofs, 2006, (1 folder) (Box 128)
      - General, 2006 (Box 128)
      - Publicity and book party, 2006 (Box 128)
      - Reviews, 2006-2007 (Box 128)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 128)
  - Plays and screenplays (Box 128)
    - "Art Buchwald's Great Interlocking Conspiracy," circa 1968 (Box 128)
    - "Art Buchwald's Washington" or "Son of the Great Society," 1965-1966, (2 folders) (Box 128)
    - "Bonjour Tristesse," undated (Box 128)
    - "The Cannibal Is Coming," 1965-1967, (1 folder) (Box 128)
    - "The Cannibal Is Coming," 1965-1967, (2 folders) (Box 129)
    - "The Fifteenth Woman," 1962 (Box 129)
    - "The Four Lives of Art Buchwald," circa 2003, (2 folders) (Box 129)
    - "The Hawks, the Doves, and the Chickens," 1969 (Box 129)
    - "Long Live Lily," 1956, (3 folders) (Box 129)
    - "Look Away, Dixieland," 1976-1981, (2 folders) (Box 130)
    - No Love Atoll, 1948, 1993, (3 folders) (Box 130)
    - One act plays, circa 1960s-circa 1980s, (2 folders) (Box 130)
    - Sheep on the Runway (Box 130)
      - Correspondence (Box 130)
        - 1969-1970, (3 folders) (Box 130)
        - 1971-1972, 1985-1991, (2 folders) (Box 131)
      - Diary, 1969-1970 (Box 131)
      - Opening night, 1970 (Box 131)
      - Playbill issues and programs, 1969-1972, 2006 (Box 131)
      - Publicity, 1969-1970 See also Container OV 10, Poster, (2 folders) (Box 131)
      - Scrapbook, 1970 See Container OV 8, same title (Box 131)
      - Script drafts, circa 1968-1969, (3 folders) (Box 131)
      - Script drafts, circa 1968-1969, (3 folders) (Box 132)
    - "The Spy in G-Flat," 1963-1966, (2 folders) (Box 132)
    - Television scripts, circa 1960s (Box 132)
    - "To Hell with Tomorrow," 1998 (Box 132)
    - Untitled work, circa 1990s (Box 132)
    - "White Collar Sentence," 1989 (Box 132)
- Buchwald v. Paramount Pictures Corporation, 1981-1999 (Box 132-139)
  The Buchwald v. Paramount Pictures Corporation series chronicles a lawsuit Buchwald and producer, Alain Bernheim, filed against Paramount Pictures in 1988 for breach of contract in the development of a film treatment. The suit was filed in the state of California on Buchwald’s claim that Paramount Pictures based their film Coming to America on his and Bernheim’s treatment titled “King for a Day,” thereby violating their contract agreements providing them compensation and credit if Paramount Pictures produced a movie based on their creative work. Buchwald was ultimately awarded damages in 1992. This series comprehensively documents the legal proceedings of the suit and includes draft copies of Buchwald's "King for a Day" and the screenplay directly based on his treatment, the initial complaint filed in 1988, briefs, motions, memoranda, depositions, and court transcripts. Correspondence from friends and colleagues reflect reactions to the suit and its outcome and a collection of clippings and a scrapbook chronicle press coverage of the case.
  Material types include briefs, correspondence, dispositions, memoranda, motions, newspaper clippings, and transcripts.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1981-1986, (2 folders) (Box 132)
  - 1987-1989, (6 folders) (Box 133)
  - 1988-1989, (8 folders) (Box 134)
  - 1989-1990, (6 folders) (Box 135)
  - 1990, (6 folders) (Box 136)
  - 1990-1991 See also Container OV 9, Scrapbook (circa 1990), (8 folders) (Box 137)
  - 1991-1994, (9 folders) (Box 138)
  - 1994-1999, undated, (9 folders) (Box 139)
- Administrative File, 1953-2006 (Box 140-176)
  The Administrative File documents Buchwald’s management of his career, finances, and public persona. This series extensively chronicles Buchwald’s financial status, speaking engagement logistics, and publishing matters such as copyrights, royalties, and syndication. A chronological file focuses on Buchwald’s speaking engagements and finances and includes contracts, correspondence with event organizers, travel itineraries, monthly expense records, and monthly financial statements, which list sources of income, net worth, and expenses. Evidence of Buchwald’s public persona and celebrity is found in a publicity file, which comprises newspaper clippings featuring articles about Buchwald, biographical material, interview transcripts, and digital audio and video files of interviews with Buchwald, especially toward the end of his life while in hospice care. Contracts, storyboards, correspondence, programs, brochures, and screenplays reflecting a number of television, radio, stage, and screen production projects are also found in this series and include correspondence and program synopses of Buchwald’s radio program Buchwald On. Projects documented in this series range from Buchwald’s active involvement and creative participation to projects where he granted permission to others to use his works. Material in this series reflects Buchwald’s involvement in production projects from an administrative perspective and does not include Buchwald’s creative works. Researchers should consult the Writings series for Buchwald’s creative works as an author and playwright and the Speeches series for transcripts of Buchwald’s remarks at speaking engagements.
  Material types include contracts, copyright renewals, correspondence, digital files, expense reports, financial statements, itineraries, newspaper clippings, photographs, and royalty statements.
  Arranged alphabetically by topic or material type. File structure of the digital content included in this series was maintained as received.
  - Authors' League of America, 1965-1969 (Box 140)
  - Chronological file (Box 140)
    - 1962-1974, (11 folders) (Box 140)
    - 1974-1986, (12 folders) (Box 141)
    - 1986-1987, (11 folders) (Box 142)
    - 1987, (8 folders) (Box 143)
    - 1987-1988, (8 folders) (Box 144)
    - 1988-1990, (7 folders) (Box 145)
    - 1990-1991, (8 folders) (Box 146)
    - 1991-1992, (8 folders) (Box 147)
    - 1992, (7 folders) (Box 148)
    - 1992-1993, (8 folders) (Box 149)
    - 1993-1994, (8 folders) (Box 150)
    - 1994, (7 folders) (Box 151)
    - 1994-1995, (8 folders) (Box 152)
    - 1995-1996, (8 folders) (Box 153)
    - 1996, (7 folders) (Box 154)
    - 1996-1997, (8 folders) (Box 155)
    - 1997-1999, (10 folders) (Box 156)
    - 2002-2005, (1 folder) (Box 157)
  - Contracts (Box 157)
    - 1953-1995, (9 folders) (Box 157)
    - 1996-2003, (2 folders) (Box 158)
  - Financial management
    - Investments, 1975-2004 (Box 158)
    - Julius Lefkowitz and Company, 1980-1984 (Box 158)
    - Miscellany, 1956, 1973-2004 (Box 158)
    - Starr and Company, 1984-2003, (2 folders) (Box 158)
    - Wallin, Simon, Black and Company (Box 158)
      - 1983, (2 folders) (Box 158)
      - 1985-1993, (1 folder) (Box 159)
  - Production projects (Box 159)
    - Audio recordings, 1960-1989 (Box 159)
    - Audio recordings - Sex and the College Boy, 1964, mss86197_178_003
    - Miscellany, 1960-1969 (Box 159)
    - Radio (Box 159)
      - Buchwald On: The Art Buchwald Radio Program, CoMedia Productions, Ltd. (Box 159)
        - Correspondence, 1968-1969, (2 folders) (Box 159)
        - Miscellany, 1969 See also Container OV 1, Cigar (Box 159)
        - Program synopses, 1969-1971, (6 folders) (Box 159)
      - General, 1962-1985 (Box 159)
    - Screen (Box 160)
      - "All Spooked Out," Tardy-Green Productions, Ltd., and Alma Productions, Inc., 1993 (Box 160)
      - American Parade, CBS News, 1983-1984 (Box 160)
      - Bill Melendez Productions, Inc., 1969-1976 See also Container OV 10, Storyboard illustrations (Box 160)
      - British Broadcasting Corp., 1979-1981 (Box 160)
      - "The Buchwald-Capp Report," Irving Gitlin Productions, Inc., 1965 (Box 160)
      - The Entertainers, CBS Television Network, 1964 (Box 160)
      - Fine Arts Films, Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 160)
      - "I Was a Beard for Errol Flynn, and I Found God," production and treatment offers, 1976-1990, (2 folders) (Box 160)
      - MGM Entertainment Co., 1963-1967 (Box 160)
      - "Paris After Dark," screenplay (treatment for "Four Letters from Paris"), 1957-1959, (2 folders) (Box 160)
      - P.S. from Paris, screenplay by John Kohn, Howard Leeds, and Julian Moore, undated (Box 160)
      - Richard Williams, Ltd., Washington Post advertisement, circa 1979 See Container OV 7, Animation celluloids (Box 161)
      - Television offers (general), 1974-1984 (Box 161)
    - Stage (Box 161)
      - The Art of Living, Oscar Lewenstein, Ltd., and Donmar Productions, Ltd., 1956-1961 See also Container OV 10, Poster, (4 folders) (Box 161)
      - Bollo the Leopard: An Endangered Species Fable, DramaDiaries Unlimited, 1975 (Box 161)
      - An Evening without Buchwald or, Where Is Art?, The Wits' End Players, Atlanta, Ga., 1976 (Box 161)
      - "Impeach Art Buchwald," Stephanie Sills Productions, Inc., 1967 (Box 161)
      - Liberal Art! A Buchwald Showcase, Cape Cod Community College, Cape Cod, Mass., 2002 (Box 161)
      - Red, White, and Buchwald, Georgetown University Theatre, Washington, D.C., 1974 (Box 162)
    - William Morris Agency, 1969-1970 (Box 162)
  - Publicity
    - Biographical material, 1965, 1981-2002, (2 folders) (Box 162)
    - Biographical questionnaires, 1977, 1989 (Box 162)
    - Biography, "Art Buchwald: The Wit of Washington," A&E Television Networks (Box 162)
      - Planning material, 1996-1998, (2 folders) (Box 162)
      - Video files, 1998, mss86197_178_005
    - Clippings (Box 162)
      - 1949-1959, (7 folders) (Box 162)
      - 1960-1967, (13 folders) (Box 163)
      - 1967-1973, (13 folders) (Box 164)
      - 1974-1981, (12 folders) (Box 165)
      - 1981-1987, (11 folders) (Box 166)
      - 1988-2006, undated, (10 folders) (Box 167)
    - Interview audio files
      - The Diane Rehm Show
        - 2006 Feb. 24, mss86197_178_009
        - 2006 Nov. 11, mss86197_178_217
      - Jim Bohannon Show, 2005 Nov., mss86197_178_222
      - Reader's Digest, Maureen Mackie, 2006 Dec., mss86197_178_012
    - Interview transcripts, 1969-1996, undated, (5 folders) (Box 167)
    - Interview video files
      - AARP Broadcast News, "Art Buchwald and End of Life Planning," 2006, mss86197_178_006
      - CBS News Sunday Morning, 2006 Dec. 17, mss86197_178_016